

FRESHER FRONTEND

I am a Fresher frontend web developer. I have graduated and have more than 1 year of Frontend Programming (ReactJS+)

websites. I can work on many different types of designs. Thank

experience, I have various skills in UI, UX, Responsive



(84+) 702378854

vvtruong1007@gmail.com

♠ Quang Nam, Viet Nam

https://github.com/vov antruong

https://vovantruong.github.io/portfolio/

## **SKILLS**

HTML, CSS3, JS

ReactJS, Redux,..

Bootstrap, UI & UX

Github, smartgit

# **EXPERIENCE**

vou recruiter!

#### INTERNS FRONTEND

Onicorn Communication Joint Stock Company. 11/2021 - 04/2022

 NFT trading and exchange website Participate in Participate in coding the interface for a crypto website, join and update wallet link method using specified API

#### FRESHER FRONTEND

Isaigon marketing C.o. 06/2022 - 06/2023

- Participate in the design of projects in terms of user interface, landing page, blog and a litle coding open source Wordpress.
- Website interface code according to the available design for web types, payment functions, authentication, ...

### **INTEREST**

- Read a book
- Listen to music
- Play football
- Play video game

### **EDUCATION**

Thu Duc College Of Technology

- Time: 09/2019 ~ 06/2023
- GPA: 7.4/10
- Major: Web Programming

